export const questions = [
  {
    passingScore: 70,
    averageTime: [0,0,56] //[hours, minutes, seconds]
  },
  {
    question: "What was the Black Death?",
    answers: {
      a: "A volcanic eruption",
      b: "A plague pandemic",
      c: "A major war",
      d: "A famine"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b",
    type: "multipleChoice",
    image: "https://dryuc24b85zbr.cloudfront.net/tes/resources/6313308/image?width=500&height=500&version=1611147338619"
  },
  {
    question: "In which century did the Black Death occur?",
    answers: {
      a: "13th century",
      b: "14th century",
      c: "15th century",
      d: "16th century"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b",
    type: "checkmark"
  },
  {
    question: "Is Yersinia pestis the bacterium of the Black Death?",
    answers: {
      a: "True",
      b: "False"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a",
    type: 'trueFalse'
  },
  {
    question: "Which animal is commonly associated with spreading the Black Death?",
    answers: {
      a: "Dogs",
      b: "Rats",
      c: "Pigs",
      d: "Cats"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Which part of the world was most affected by the Black Death?",
    answers: {
      a: "Asia",
      b: "Europe",
      c: "Africa",
      d: "Americas"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "What percentage of Europe's population is estimated to have died from the Black Death?",
    answers: {
      a: "10-20%",
      b: "30-60%",
      c: "70-80%",
      d: "5-10%"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "What was one of the major social impacts of the Black Death?",
    answers: {
      a: "Increased birth rates",
      b: "Decline in religious faith",
      c: "Rise in feudalism",
      d: "Expansion of trade"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Which symptom was NOT typically associated with the Black Death?",
    answers: {
      a: "Buboes",
      b: "High fever",
      c: "Loss of limbs",
      d: "Chills"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "How did the Black Death spread so quickly across Europe?",
    answers: {
      a: "Trade routes",
      b: "Wildfires",
      c: "Earthquakes",
      d: "Climate change"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "Which medical practice was commonly used during the Black Death but was largely ineffective?",
    answers: {
      a: "Vaccination",
      b: "Bloodletting",
      c: "Antibiotics",
      d: "Chemotherapy"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  }
];
